{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722639504","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722639503"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722640576","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722640576"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHESABU"," userResponse":" KUHESABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722641490","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722641490"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBA"," userResponse":" NAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722644668","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722644668"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722645162","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722645162"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722645785","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722645785"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722648829","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722648829"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722649622","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722649622"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722650016","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722650015"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722650749","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722650749"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722653843","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722653842"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722654466","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722654466"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722654999","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722654999"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722658008","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722658008"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722658081","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722658081"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_064750"," gameId":" fb91cf33-fed3-4b18-803c-29d0878d2f99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}